Hello Hello Friends this is my channel and
Darbar Digital Studio and Online Service
and in this I will guide you CSC Insurance,
how to do insurance from C, which
company to do it from, how it is third party, how it is
first party, so
let's start, do subscribe to the channel
Hello Hello Friends welcome you all again to my channel
and I have come again to
guide you on insurance, so today we will do
insurance from this number
in ICICI Lombard from third party motor company for
that passenger vehicle, commercial vehicle,
miscellaneous vehicle, tractor, JCB,
other so let's start first of all I have to go to
insurance,
after CSC login I have to do CSC login and I have already
explained the rest of the process in the video,
you will get the description link,
so let's go again to motor third
party, right now I am guiding you to third party, after
all my third party guide, after having
third party site of all the companies, I will
tell you
how to do party, so let's go to such a
long and thick third party I am in the
private company which is in Indore and  The
branch office is in Ratlam, we do
n't have a branch office in India,
so let's get started. So
friends, we've logged in and we've come to the
iPartner dashboard, where
you can see a lot of
search facilities, there's a search facility here. There's an
option for animals. If you click on your name, it will
show you all the insurance details.
From here, you can call the customer. This
means you can see someone's insurance premium. If you
submit it here, you can
see it here. You won't have to work so hard.
Let's start. Two-wheeler
motor. Let me tell you that
in the passenger category, the private cars that are used for
cleaning the school,
those are appointed
chapters. Poclains are more machines that are
used in agriculture. These are called
miscellaneous.
So, let's start.
We have to do the full code from the motor two-wheeler,
like we will open the gate and quote. Here, you will
see
that the third party, standalone audio policy,
Vishu, puncture channel mode policy. So,
now we are doing third party, so there is
no problem.  Otherwise, the
standalone no deposit scheme here is that the
vehicles which are being sold now are
five years old, so there is a
one year old TP and in diminished on
road there is a 4 year TP,
in TV third party, so to
renew the one year old TP, we will have to click yes here, let it remain here,
first of all we have to enter the vehicle number here, we will enter the
vehicle number and
you have to enter the vehicle number correctly, you have to get ITO details,
like we will enter the positive details here,
it will
take the details from your MP Transport side through audio, you have to enter it here, okay, the
registration date has to be
entered by looking at the RC of the vehicle or you
can enter it from MP Transport also, I have
told you about this earlier also, it is
not adding a reminder in my system, that is why I am
making a video from my mobile, this is to help you people,
now we have to select the manufacturer
and in the manufacturer, I have a Hero
car, two wheeler,
then you select Hero  You have to do that,
select Hero Honda's family vehicles,
Hero Honda is old, you have to select the nodal in Hero Honda, so
this net is a bit
slow, Shivling is a
planned, hey my car,
friend, now you have to do it, after that as soon as
you do ok, here you will be given the
option of showroom price IDV, it will tell you in this ID, I will tell you
here its ghee value at that time is coming,
50,000, right now the company is also keeping ID
24500, okay, it can be decreased or
increased, I will tell you that later,
here in the state you have to do Madhya Pradesh,
we will do ok for Madhya Pradesh and here the
polish type will remain normal, 10-hour
means for how many years you have to do it,
keep one, two, three by default, it is
not done for 3 years, because the premium will become big,
then no one will get such expensive insurance done, the
receiver in the manufacturer has to be
entered and the description has to be left,
in the current registration, individual has to be entered, if the
vehicle is in the name of any company, like
my company is Mahak Agro Industries, then
I am here  But I will select the company, otherwise I have to
keep it as individual. Okay, and this insurance cover,
about which I have already given information, is a
personal accidental cover. In this, if the person who is
not driving the vehicle will be covered, if
his date is fulfilled, then
he will get Rs. 15 lakhs. So this has not been done yet, if we remove the cover, then it will happen.
Okay, right now I have already folded it. On hold, okay.
If you want to take Khedi channel, then
IMT option is available under additional cover. You
can try additional cover. In this, you will get cover in different
ways. And if you find an unknown
messenger or an unknown person driving the vehicle, then there will be
cover for that too. For this, there will be cover for
different professions. Yes, then this will
increase your premium. Have you heard that decoration
[music] will
also be covered? No, it is an old vehicle, do
not keep the additional cover.
After keeping it, we will move ahead and you do
not have to keep discount or loading
discount. If you say yes, then you will get the option of
adding this tip to third party property and
leave Yasmin here. So do
not do this.  The premium will increase now, okay,
Prince Polish, you have to keep it as available,
so who knows whether you had insurance before or not, if it has
expired, okay,
now as we do, the
premium will come here, we have to back up the premium,
here it will tell you how much is being charged for which,
okay, this is
becoming basic, basic policy and
third party, and it is telling both, so we had to do
only third party, so we will do this, it has been done
and this is becoming our normal policy,
choose it, it will have the entire vehicle
insurance, now if you feel that the
premium is high then what you have to do is go
to the ex-showroom conversion, as soon as you
go here, a new text will
open, now it is in the tape that
we will have to see the highest value first, and if the diversion is from 40 to 50,
then we can make it 40, where those promotions are
coming now,
what can we sell, we have
happened to
Ajay,
now we have to continue,
as soon as we continue, it will come to you 40001
showroom, now you have to submit,
submit  After this you will have to do the
gate quota again, okay I will do the
gate quote once more,
if the premium decreases then it is good, otherwise
you will have to keep this ID as well, okay,
after that the next process is that you have to enter the engine number,
chassis number from the MP Transport side,
which I will tell you,
or
you can enter the inch number by taking the old policy, if you have entered it then
enter it now, after that if the
vehicle is taken on loan or hypothecation, if it is financed then you
have to mark it as yes, then
enter the finance details, otherwise you have to
proceed further, you can enter the nominee in 9 months,
okay, this is compulsory, if something happens to the dishonor tomorrow, then only if there is a nominee,
his
claim will prevail, okay, we will do this,
here in this post,
okay, there is a
new customer in the customer details,
if you want to stop someone from staying with you, then
you can do it here, okay,
now you have to enter the address, the address of the person,
as soon as you fill  We will do the
date of birth and marking, here the
name of the governor will come, do it,
you have to enter the date of birth, as
soon as you enter it,
you have to pin the address, turn it on here,
I have already told you this in the previous video,
it will automatically give the details, you have to
enter the pin code, you do not have to enter the email, the
mobile number is compulsory, we enter the mobile number,
okay, if it is a PAN number then it is fine, otherwise it is okay,
leave this number, if you want to forget the proposal,
I have to tell this email IDs compulsory, okay,
we enter it, here if it is
not of any customer then you can enter yours also, there is no
problem,
updates will come on this, regarding this policy,
you can also get the soft copy of the policy,
as if we will make a proposal, okay, that is done,
now if
you will do this proposal once more, the
proposal ID has come, now you have to click on the policy, okay, if you will do the
policy like this brother,
now you will be asked to make the payment,
it has come from C, okay, as soon as
I make the payment you  So the quality will be downloaded,
then you can give it to everyone here or color
print out or black and white top
to the customer, so such motor ICC will make the
two wheeler into inches and
so if you liked my video then
you can subscribe to me, like it, if you have
any problem with the video then you
can comment me, so let's end the video here, the
video has become long,
okay friends, thank you.